Petrol and diesel prices have now increased again.
Know how much will be available per litre now, the
real impact of the Middle East crisis.  Yes
friends, it is now visible on Indians.
Oil marketing companies have increased the prices
of petrol and diesel for the fourth time in the last two weeks.  This is the
fourth increase in petrol and diesel prices within 10 days.
With this increase, the
price of petrol in the capital Delhi has crossed ₹100
per liter and
according to the news agencies, the
price of petrol in Delhi has increased from ₹2 to
61 paise per liter.  This means that
petrol will now cost ₹102 in Delhi.   The
prices have also been increased by ₹2
and ₹71 per litre.  Now the
price of diesel in Delhi is ₹95.  has increased by ₹20 and here in
Chennai the price of petrol per litre has increased by
₹2 and here it has increased by 46 paise.   The
peak heat wave in Rajasthan reached 47°C.
Alert:
Weather may change here after May 28.  Yes
friends, the
heat and heat wave will continue in Rajasthan for the next four days.  The Meteorological
Department has issued Orange Alert or Yellow Alert in many districts.  The
mercury may reach 47°.
Whereas with the rains coming after 28th May, the
heat is now increasing to its peak here in Rajasthan.  The
Meteorological Department has warned
that the temperature in many districts may rise
above 47 degrees Celsius in the coming days.
IIM Udaipur report will deceive you.
Yes friends, 657%
here people do not have emergency money
and after leaving the job,
their house can last only for so many months.  Yes
friends, many shocking revelations in the report
of IIM Udaipur regarding the financial preparedness of the families of Rajasthan.
On Uttar Pradesh Chief Minister Adityanath Yogi's statement on Namaz, Iqrar Hasan said
that roads are also the property of our society.   Yes
friends, while commenting on the statement of Kerala MP Iqrar Hasan
regarding the CM not offering namaz on the road in UP, he has
said that he has no right to do anything like this.
Important decisions were taken today in the meeting of the Central Government under the chairmanship of the Prime Minister and the
meeting of the Central Government was held here.   The
works in various ministries
were reviewed and the progress of development projects was
discussed and many new
projects can also be considered here.
Meteorological Department alert:
Meteorological Department has issued a warning regarding intense heat and heat wave in many states of the country.
Yes friends, people are
advised to avoid going out of the house after noon and drink adequate water.
New security of Railways: Indian Railways
is preparing to introduce modern coaches and better digital services in many trains for the convenience of passengers and through this the journey can be
made more comfortable.   There
is news of great relief for the farmers and to
strengthen the agriculture sector here, the
government has taken
many initiatives and announced to connect the farmers with modern technology and irrigation facilities.   A
big change has been seen in the field of education.
New
smart meters and online
learning platforms have been introduced in classrooms to promote digital education in many schools across the country.   To
promote tourism,
facilities can be improved at major tourist destinations in the country
so that more and more tourists can be
attracted and the local
economy can also benefit.
India thrashed Pakistan in UAE.
Afghanistan and Bangladesh have mentioned
that the country with history here is Narsingh. The
United Nations, America and India have
responded in strong words to Pakistan,
saying that serious questions have been raised on their history policies.
India has said
that a country which is itself
surrounded by allegations of genocide and partition,
how can it accuse others.  Does
not possess moral authority.
India
reiterated its stance on Pakistan with reference to Afghanistan and Bangladesh.
[Music]
Tight security at the West Bengal Falta assembly seat.
Yes friends, after the
controversy in the reconstructed assembly constituency,
after the controversy over EVMs, the Election
Commission was alerted and
major action was taken this morning in the Falta assembly seat of West Bengal.  The
Election Commission has decided to conduct re-polling after allegations of severe EVM tampering and electoral irregularities.
Voting started at 7:00 am
and
35 more companies of central forces have been deployed here for security.  A
total of six candidates are in the fray for the seat.
Chakka Jam in Delhi NCR, airport
strike today.  Supplies and services for daily use are
likely to be affected.  Due to the impact on
commercial vehicle operations in Delhi NCR and surrounding states, prices of
vegetables,
milk and other items may also be increased.   Let us
tell you that Prime Minister Narendra
Modi has been shown as a snake charmer in a Norwegian newspaper.
What
is written here about Prime Minister Narendra Modi?
Know the complete information with us.
Where is the highest temperature in the country at 48 degrees?  What is the situation in Delhi, UP, Bihar
this week?  Know with us.
More than 15 lakh medical
staff on strike across the country today.  Know these are the eight demands
of the government.
Congress extended its hand towards BSP,
but Mayawati refused to meet.
Yes friends, the assembly elections in Uttar Pradesh
may be next year, but political
claims are still in the air.
Oil prices will crash.  Trump's
claim came to light.  Now the war in Iran will end.
According to the CAG report, the
Bhajan Lal government of Rajasthan has so far been able to
spend only half of the budget allocated for development in the last financial year.   The
earth and the swinging sky here and the mercury has
crossed 48 degrees.  Yes
friends, IMD has issued heat wave alerts for the next 4 days to 5
days in Eastern Rajasthan, Central India and
parts of Uttar Pradesh, Haryana, Delhi, Punjab, Eastern Gujarat and Maharashtra.
Health related problems are
increasing.
Heat wave is wreaking havoc in many parts of the country and
according to the Indian Meteorological Department (IMD), the
temperature was recorded at 45°C in Delhi and 46°C in Nagpur.  At the same time,
in some areas the mercury crossed 48°.  The
IMD has issued a severe heat wave alert for the next four to five
days in parts of eastern Rajasthan and central India,
north India and
some areas of Haryana, Delhi, Punjab, eastern Gujarat and Maharashtra.
Amidst claims of delay in Panchayat elections in Uttar Pradesh, a big decision of the Yogi government
came to light.  Yes friends, the
formation of Backward Classes Commission has been approved.
Know how the reservation was decided.  Yes
friends, let us tell you that the Uttar Pradesh
government has taken a big step before the Panchayat elections and has
formed a dedicated Backward Class Commission to decide the rural bodies and OBC reservation here.
Before the Panchayat elections in Uttar Pradesh, a
major initiative has been taken by the government regarding reservation in rural bodies
and in compliance with the orders of the Supreme Court, the
state government has
constituted a Backward Class Commission dedicated to the state local and rural bodies.   The
objective of the Commission here is to examine the social and administrative backwardness of the three-tier
Panchayati bodies and Other Backward Classes i.e.
OBCs to provide them reservation.
Donald Trump bought shares worth billions in 90 days,
America was shaken,
Wall Stein was surprised in the report.  Yes friends,
Trump has bought at
least 1 million US dollars worth of
shares of companies like Oracle and Microsoft and Bag for this very quarter.  His portfolio
also includes shares of companies like Amazon, Mita and here and US
President Donald Trump or his
advisors have added more than Rs 33,000 crore to the stock in the first three months of this year.
After this revelation, a
new investigation has started against Trump.
This means that even the experts of level law and stick have been surprised in the training activity.  This has
again raised the issue of conflict of interest in Washington and
this is the first to be revealed here by Bloomberg.  In
which crores of dollars have been given to some big companies of America i.e.
technology and finance and
associate and media companies.
Diesel and petrol will become more expensive and will not be able to buy Russian oil.
India-US concession ends.
In the midst of the Homo crisis, the US has relaxed the rules by waiving the restrictions for some time.
This has allowed the Russian Federation to purchase cargoes that have been loaded into the country without any
immediate penalty.
Due to the blockade, the oil crisis in the world is deepening.
But there does
n't seem to be a solution to this.  Although initially the
US has removed the oil and gas embargoes imposed on some countries.   Including
Russian.  Therefore, India is
continuously buying oil from Russia and the country is
facing oil shortage.  India
is facing the second worst oil shock and
now the window is closing for America and India.
Illegal voting took place in the assembly elections of this state.
10 foreign nationals arrested.  Know the
latest updates.  Yes friends, let us tell you
that the complaint was lodged by the officials during the tenure of the Guest and Chennai
Police Commissioner here
and the case was registered between 7th to 14th May by the Central Crime Branch
and local police units
here.
Chennai police recently
arrested four women here for allegedly using fraudulently obtained documents to cast their votes illegally in the Sampath and Tamil Nadu Assembly elections.
One was a press release and the other was intercepted at the
Chennai
International Airport here while trying to leave the country after the April 23 elections.
Why did Bengal CM start crying in the morning? He took a
special oath to remember the wounds he received 11 days ago.  Yes friends, West Bengal
Chief Minister Swadhruva Adhikari
suddenly reached Kulap village in Chandipur on Sunday
and where he expressed his condolences to the family of his divine and
soul helper and Chandranath Rath.
Chandranath was brutally shot dead in Madhya village 11 days ago.  As soon as he
reached home, the
Chief Minister could not control his tears
and became emotional after holding the hand of his crying elderly mother.
Five-day waking system will be started in banks across the country.
Yes friends, a
big update has come amid PM Modi's appeal.   There has been a
long-standing demand from RBI Bank Union to implement a 5-day working week.
But now a
letter has also been written to PM Modi in this matter.
What will happen in the whole matter from now on
?  Update:
Big good news and important
news is coming for lakhs of bank employees of the country.  Those working five days in banks, that is, the
entire demand for five day working has again increased.  All
India Bank Officers have reached here
and later by writing a letter directly to Prime Minister Narendra
Modi, the long pending
proposals were implemented immediately
and the bank officers' organization here
says that now the time has come when the demands of 5 days
working week and employees are
not being met but should be seen in the interest of the country.
This step will not only provide
relief to the employees but will also lead to fuel
conservation and energy saving and
increase work efficiency in banks.
Bulldozers will run across the entire country.
Why has BJP minister Dilip Ghosh said this after the bulldozer action in Bengal?
After the formation of BJP government in West Bengal, bulldozer action against illegal encroachment and illegal
construction has intensified.  The
campaign has been launched at Howrah station and here in the area of ​​Til district of Kolkata.
Whereas Minister Dilip Ghosh has
warned of strict action across the state.
After the formation of BJP government in West Bengal, bulldozers are being used on illegal encroachments
and here bulldozers have also been used on illegal encroachments around
Ganga Ghat and bus stand outside Howrah station.
Two days work from home order in Uttar Pradesh.
Yes friends, 2 years imprisonment to Azam Khan is
our mistake.  Slogans of pen flowers.  Yes
friends, many important events have taken place in Uttar Pradesh
today, ranging from politics to administration,
crime and development, education, health and
weather.
Many major incidents and headlines related to different districts of the state have
also come to light.  Which will have a direct impact
on the lives of the common people.  Let us know
all the news together.
Today's biggest and important news of Uttar Pradesh.
Government teachers of Rajasthan will now be
promoted.  You will get good news after a long wait.  Yes
friends, the
education department of Rajasthan is going to give good news to
1000 third class employees who are looking for career growth and promotion.
Due to the long standing issues of senior MLAs and various court cases and administrative delays, the DCP process has come to a complete
standstill.  It has now been given the green signal by the
Director of Secondary Education and here in Bikaner
and now the department has prepared a
new seniority list taking the position as on April 1, 2022 as the basis.  The
Education
Department has taken this big step not only for the
protection and social reform of teachers
but also for filling up the vacant posts of
Secondary Education Minister and
Second Grade of Higher Secondary Schools
and thousands of posts of recruitments in the entire state.
Prime Minister Narendra Modi held day-
long land talks here.  Yes
friends, increasing digital and green partnership,
Prime Minister Narendra Modi held delegation level talks with
Netherlands Prime Minister Rab Jetten on Saturday.
Meanwhile, discussions have been held between the two countries on
strengthening cooperation in areas such as semiconductor and digital technology and education innovation and understanding.
Amidst the appeal of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, the
new minister reached Varanasi with a huge convoy.  Yes friends,
after the video went viral, the opposition has
now targeted the BJP minister
and this is the situation when
all the leaders are cautioning him.
But its financial
and impact on the common people is to be known and here
Prime Minister Narendra Modi has made a strong appeal to the
countrymen to use big vehicles judiciously to reduce the country's fuel consumption and use it judiciously.
Where the message of fuel saving is being given by the country's leaders, ministers and
officials by limiting their convoys to their own convenience.
CNG prices increased again in Delhi NCR.  Yes
friends, know how much the
increase has been.  What will happen next?
Know the complete information with us.  And let us tell you here that today
once
again the prices of CNG have been increased by NCR.
Now CNG has become costlier by ₹1.  Know the
meaning of CNG prices:
People living in Delhi and NCR have once again been
hit by inflation.  CNG
prices have been increased once again in Delhi NCR.
And here CNG has become costlier by ₹1 per kg.
Before this, gas
companies had increased the price by ₹22.  That means,
overall, CNG has become costlier by ₹3 within 3 days.   Is the
Prime Minister's appeal for austerity putting the economy in crisis?  Yes,
friends, know what they say.